New England Medical Center Records MS099
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Architectural/Engineering Services records, 1982 -- 1990; MS099.011; 12.0 Linear Feet
  This series primarily contains project files for minor renovation projects, but also includes architectural drawings and meeting minutes. The project files contain correspondence, specifications, plans, memos, transmittal forms, and invoices, as well as documentation of changes proposed by Barr & Barr for the "Scamper" renovation project of the Jackson and Center buildings. Architectural drawings for the The Pratt Diagnostic Hospital building and a few architectural plans for buildings encompassing the New England Medical Center Hospital are included in this series. The Pratt Diagnostic Hospital drawings and specifications are of elevators, doors, transoms, windows, and bathrooms.
  According to Dave Nathan's Guide to the NEMC Archives, the following items are missing: Slides of Proger building furnishings, 1973.
  This series is arranged in 3 sub-series: Project review meeting minutes, Renovation projects, and Architectural drawings.
  - Project review meeting minutes, 1973 -- 1979; MS099.011.001; 1.2 Linear Feet
    - PR meeting minutes, 1973; MS099.011.001.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - PR meeting minutes, 1974; MS099.011.001.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - PR meeting minutes, 1975; MS099.011.001.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - PR meeting minutes, 1979; MS099.011.001.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Renovation project files, 1982 -- 1990; MS099.011.002; 12.0 Linear Feet
    Files are mostly arranged by building. Files for Biewend building may be found in box 22. Files for the BD and BFH may be found in box 23. Files for the PC/NECH may be found in box 24. Files for the Rehabilitation Center may be found in box 25. Files for the Proger building may be found in boxes 25 and 28. Files for the Ziskind building may be found in boxes 28 and 29.
    - Barr and Barr inoivces and payment approvals, phase 6, 1978 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - HVAC and improvements, Gross Anatomy, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Emergency room specifications, 1976; MS099.011.002.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - Blood Bank specifications, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - Microbiology, Phase II specifications, 1970; MS099.011.002.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Radiotherapy Oncology specifications, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.011.002.021.00010 (Box 21)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine Cancer Research Center Bed Unit specifications, 1973; MS099.011.002.021.00011 (Box 21)
    - Technical Handbook for Facilities Engineering and Construction Manual, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.021.00012 (Box 21)
      Part 2 - Federally Assisted Activities Information for Project Applicants and State Agencies on Deisgn and Construction Related Activities
    - T-NEMC Rehab-Holmes Alley Corridor Calculations, 1974; MS099.011.002.021.00013; Barnes and Jarnis, Inc. (Box 21)
    - Phase II renovations, School of Medicine specifications, 1970; MS099.011.002.021.00014 (Box 21)
    - Cancer Research Center Bed Unit specifications, addendum 1, 1973; MS099.011.002.022.00001; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 22)
    - Ziskind Animal Room specifications, 1973; MS099.011.002.022.00002 (Box 22)
    - Ziskind Animal Room specifications with addendum, 1973; MS099.011.002.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - General and Supplementary Conditions of the Contract for Construction, 1970 -- 1972; MS099.011.002.022.00004; American Institute of Architects (Box 22)
    - Estimates, 1976 -- 1981; MS099.011.002.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - Assisted renovations project, 1967 -- 1970; MS099.011.002.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - NEMCH gross square feet PRF no. 500, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.011.002.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - Inventory drawings, 1963 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00008 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - accounting move, 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00009 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - drawings, 1971 -- 1976; MS099.011.002.022.00010 (Box 22)
    - Biewend building - general file, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.011.002.022.00011 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - stair expressway, 1975; MS099.011.002.022.00012 (Box 22)
    - Memos/letters, 1978 -- 1981; MS099.011.002.022.00013 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Adult Psychiatry office, 1970; MS099.011.002.022.00014 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - day hospital, 1975 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00015 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - day hospital estimates and memos, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00016 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Neuro-Ophthalmology Dr. Gittinger, 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00017 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - substance abuse, 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00018 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - runaway adolescent girl day care center, 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00019 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - runaway adolescent girl day care center budget file, 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00020 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - dialysis clinic, 1978; MS099.011.002.022.00021 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - dialysis clinic payments, 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00022 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - room 328 psychiatry department, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00023 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Robson's office, 1978; MS099.011.002.022.00024 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Robson's office, carpeting and furniture, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00025 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Robson's office, shades, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00026 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Robson's office, drawings, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00027 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Stombler's office, drawings and estimates, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00028 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - pediatric eye clinic, 1971; MS099.011.002.022.00029 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - psychiatric in-patient, 1971; MS099.011.002.022.00030 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - drawings and catalogs, MS099.011.002.022.00031 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - sketches and site notes, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00032 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Rosenthal's office, MS099.011.002.022.00033 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - transmittals, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00034 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - calculations and record drawings, MS099.011.002.022.00035 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - budget, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00036 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - furniture, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00037 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Psychiatry department, estimates, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00038 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Psychiatry department, memos and letters, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00039 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - L.E.A.A. project, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00040 (Box 22)
    - Department of Medicine curved wall specifications, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00041 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dermatology offices, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00042 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - lobby renovation, 1972; MS099.011.002.022.00043 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Ophthalmology department, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.011.002.022.00044 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Ophthalmology department expansion, 1976 -- 1978; MS099.011.002.022.00045 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Ophthalmology department dark room, 1972; MS099.011.002.022.00046 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Biochemistry lab proposal, 1976; MS099.011.002.022.00047 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Rosenthal's office, 1975; MS099.011.002.022.00048 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - TMCA professional billing budget, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00049 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - TMCA professional bill file A/S, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00050 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - TMCA radiology billing, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00051 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - originals 20th scale schematics, 1976; MS099.011.002.022.00052 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - adult psychiatry offices, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.011.002.022.00053 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - psychiatry department PRF, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00054 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Dr. Shader's office, 1980; MS099.011.002.022.00055 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Birth Defects Center A/S file, 1978; MS099.011.002.022.00056 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - mailroom estimates, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00057 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - TMCA, 1978 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00058 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - TMCA, furniture and memos, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00059 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Accounting move budget file, 1975 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.022.00060 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - Change orders and billing, 1979; MS099.011.002.022.00061 (Box 22)
    - Biewend - transmittals, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00001 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - hospital billing, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00002 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - billing offices, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00003 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - hospital billing budget, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00004 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - accounting move, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00005 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - accounting, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00006 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - financial officiers, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00007 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - personnel payroll, PRF 477, 1978; MS099.011.002.023.00008 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - personnel payroll budget file, 1978; MS099.011.002.023.00009 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - proposed offices, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00010 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - electrical, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00011 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - H.V.A.C plumbing and mechanical, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00012 (Box 23)
    - Biewend - Biomedical engineering center, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00013 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - budget file, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00014 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - pharmacy, 1982; MS099.011.002.023.00015 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - basement pharmacy, 1982; MS099.011.002.023.00016 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - A1 critchetts office, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00017 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Dr. Daoust's office, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00018 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Cystoscopy, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00019 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Rita Doucet's office, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00020 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - educational secreatries, 1976 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00021 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - edducational secretary's space, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00022 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary emergency generator, 1971; MS099.011.002.023.00023 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - eye clinic, 1971; MS099.011.002.023.00024 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Dr. Daoust's office, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00025 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary Hematology and Neurology, 1972 -- 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00026 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - offices and exam rooms, 1972; MS099.011.002.023.00027 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Ophthalmology budget, 1978; MS099.011.002.023.00028 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Pediatric admitting, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00029 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - pharmacy, 1972; MS099.011.002.023.00030 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Recovery Room, 1972; MS099.011.002.023.00031 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - Catherization, 1971; MS099.011.002.023.00032 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - color scheme, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00033 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - M/S ICU A/S file, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00034 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - inner vestibule doors budget, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00035 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - basement corridor redecorating A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00036 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - offices and clinics, Hemenway, 1970; MS099.011.002.023.00037 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - kitchen, 1969 -- 1970; MS099.011.002.023.00038 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - unit secretary's desk, A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00039 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - Pediactric waiting area, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00040 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Cystopscopy budget, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00041 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Pediactric Hematology budget, 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00042 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - dietary storage south corridor PRF A/S file, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00043 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - Pharmacy waiting area A/S file, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00044 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - inner vestibule A/S file, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00045 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital - M/S ICU budget file, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00046 (Box 23)
    - Cooper building basement, 1980; MS099.011.002.023.00047 (Box 23)
    - Cooper building basement computer conversion budget file, 1975 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.023.00048 (Box 23)
    - Computer project at Cooper electric, 1970; MS099.011.002.023.00049 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Urology suite budget, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00050 (Box 23)
    - Boston Dispensary - Urology suite, Urology Radiology, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00051 (Box 23)
    - Cooper building basement computer raised floor, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00052 (Box 23)
    - Cooper building 1st floor coffee lounge area, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00053 (Box 23)
    - Cooper buiding basement phase II, 1975; MS099.011.002.023.00054 (Box 23)
    - Cooper building electric 1st floor, 1980; MS099.011.002.023.00055 (Box 23)
    - Dr. Neurath laboratory, 1977 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00056 (Box 23)
    - Cooper building parking lot, 1982; MS099.011.002.023.00057 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital medical ICU work lists, summary sheets, 1979; MS099.011.002.023.00058 (Box 23)
    - Boston Floating Hospital pediatric waiting area, 1976; MS099.011.002.023.00059 (Box 23)
    - Carpet and flooring, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00001 (Box 24)
    - Corridor lighting, 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00002 (Box 24)
    - Draperies, 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00003 (Box 24)
    - Furniture, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00004 (Box 24)
    - Furniture lists, 1970; MS099.011.002.024.00005 (Box 24)
    - Furniture [Carolyn only] A/S, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00006 (Box 24)
    - Furniture schedule originals, 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00007 (Box 24)
    - Lighting report, 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00008 (Box 24)
    - Redecordation projects, signs, vonar, 1972 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00009 (Box 24)
    - Pratt 4 renovations, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00010 (Box 24)
    - Health Services building blue prints, 1971; MS099.011.002.024.00011 (Box 24)
    - CSR renovations budget file, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00012 (Box 24)
    - Pediatric waiting area center 4 A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00013 (Box 24)
    - Boston Dispensary pediatric x-ray A/S file, 1976 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00014 (Box 24)
    - Pediatric medical clinic center budget, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.011.002.024.00015 (Box 24)
    - Boston Dispensary - Pediatric hematology room 478 B, 1976; MS099.011.002.024.00016 (Box 24)
    - Boston Dispensary - Pediatric Admitting Servcies A/S file, 1976; MS099.011.002.024.00017 (Box 24)
    - Health Services buildling 1A plans, 1970; MS099.011.002.024.00018 (Box 24)
    - Physics Lab Pre 1-A extended, 1971; MS099.011.002.024.00019 (Box 24)
    - Cobalt room 2 Pre 1-A, 1971; MS099.011.002.024.00020 (Box 24)
    - Phase 1A, 1970; MS099.011.002.024.00021 (Box 24)
    - Pratt basement, 1975; MS099.011.002.024.00022 (Box 24)
    - Consultants, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00023 (Box 24)
    - Ladies Committee cart, 1981; MS099.011.002.024.00024 (Box 24)
    - Drawings - Pratt exterior, 1980; MS099.011.002.024.00025 (Box 24)
    - X-ray darkroom doors, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.024.00026 (Box 24)
    - Master budget, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00027 (Box 24)
    - Dr. Wolff's purchase orders, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00028 (Box 24)
    - Pratt/Farnsworth basement - C.S.R. measured drawings A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00029 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Urology - office for Ms. Flaim, 1980; MS099.011.002.024.00030 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Radiology A/S file budget estimates, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.024.00031 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Radiology Dr. Paul's suite, 1970; MS099.011.002.024.00032 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - G.I. suite A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00033 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - G.I. suite Room E3 G.E. equipment, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00034 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - G.I. suite budget file, 1978; MS099.011.002.024.00035 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - G.I. suite, 1978; MS099.011.002.024.00036 (Box 24)
    - Certificate of need, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00037 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Farnsworth X-OMAT, 1970 -- 1976; MS099.011.002.024.00038 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Farnsworth corridor and Dr. Fuleihan's office budget, 1978; MS099.011.002.024.00039 (Box 24)
    - Pratt Medical Group Hemenway - Rooms 106, 107, 112, 1982; MS099.011.002.024.00040 (Box 24)
    - 50 Herald Street, Boston, 1966; MS099.011.002.024.00041 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Urology offices, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.011.002.024.00042 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Vito Rallo office, 1971; MS099.011.002.024.00043 (Box 24)
    - Pratt medicine rooms, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00044 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Minor O.R. center core renovations budget, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00045 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Minor O.R. center core renovations A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00046 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - X-Ray A, B, C A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.024.00047 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - X-Ray Radiology dressing room, 2nd floor, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.011.002.024.00048 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - X-Ray, PO requisitions, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.011.002.024.00049 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Radiology corridor color scheme, 1978; MS099.011.002.024.00050 (Box 24)
    - Pratt - Ziskind IA interface, 1971 -- 1975; MS099.011.002.025.00001 (Box 25)
    - Radiotherapy Oncology Center H.E.W. second submission, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00002 (Box 25)
    - Radiotherapy Oncology Center second submission, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00003 (Box 25)
    - Radiotherapy Oncology Center third submission, 1972; MS099.011.002.025.00004 (Box 25)
    - EKG/EEG Proger, 1973 -- 1975; MS099.011.002.025.00005 (Box 25)
    - Proger signage proposal budget, 1975; MS099.011.002.025.00006 (Box 25)
    - Proger 3rd floor doctors office, 1975; MS099.011.002.025.00007 (Box 25)
    - Doctors offices, 1971 -- 1973; MS099.011.002.025.00008 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - 5th floor plans and estimates, 1968 -- 1969; MS099.011.002.025.00009 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - electric doors, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00010 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - exterior lettering budget file, 1978; MS099.011.002.025.00011 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - Immunology 4th floor, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00012 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - Dr. Robert Schwartz, 1972; MS099.011.002.025.00013 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - RRRT grant offices, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00014 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - 3rd floor corridor upgrade, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00015 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - 3rd floor corridor upgrade budget file, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00016 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - 3rd floor corridor upgrade, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00017 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - blood research lab budget, 1979; MS099.011.002.025.00018 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - maintenance department [basement] budget, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00019 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - hematology, 1975; MS099.011.002.025.00020 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - centrix and basement, 1975 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00021 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - redecoration, 1972 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.025.00022 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - occupational therapy A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00023 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitaiton - Emergency service, 1969 -- 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00024 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - basement, Maintenance, shops, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00025 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - Dr. Corcoran areas budget file, 1979; MS099.011.002.025.00026 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - E.M.G. and related moves, Dr. O'Toole and Ms. Bernard, 1977; MS099.011.002.025.00027 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation Oncology Center - letters and memos received, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00028 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation Oncology Center - equipment, 1971 -- 1973; MS099.011.002.025.00029 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - exterior lettering A/S file, 1978; MS099.011.002.025.00030 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - Dr. Corcoran A/S file, 1978; MS099.011.002.025.00031 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - basement survey (The Tombs), maintenance, 1971; MS099.011.002.025.00032 (Box 25)
    - Rehabilitation - EMG relocation A/S file, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.025.00033 (Box 25)
    - Proger - Spruce up tour, 1978; MS099.011.002.025.00034 (Box 25)
    - Proger - dialysis unit, 1978; MS099.011.002.025.00035 (Box 25)
    - Proger - blood bank, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.011.002.025.00036 (Box 25)
    - Proger - special proc., 1972; MS099.011.002.025.00037 (Box 25)
    - Proger - neurton beam, 1975; MS099.011.002.025.00038 (Box 25)
    - Proger - linen storage, 1976; MS099.011.002.025.00039 (Box 25)
    - Proger - room for the bereaved budget file, 1979; MS099.011.002.025.00040 (Box 25)
    - Dr. Schwartz office suite, 1971 -- 1973; MS099.011.002.025.00041 (Box 25)
    - Furnishing task force, 1970; MS099.011.002.025.00042 (Box 25)
    - Proger and Dental - medical oncology, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.025.00043 (Box 25)
    - Proger - furniture selection task force, 1970; MS099.011.002.025.00044 (Box 25)
    - Proger - simulator room certificate of need budget file, 1975 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.025.00045 (Box 25)
    - Various projects - Boston City Hospital, 1969; MS099.011.002.025.00046 (Box 25)
    - Personnel offices, 1978; MS099.011.002.025.00047 (Box 25)
    - Personnel move to 37 Bennet Street, 1976; MS099.011.002.025.00048 (Box 25)
    - 37 Bennet Street entrance budget file, 1980; MS099.011.002.026.00001 (Box 26)
    - Personnel offices, 1978; MS099.011.002.026.00002 (Box 26)
    - Bedside table, 1971; MS099.011.002.026.00003 (Box 26)
    - 37 Bennet Street darkroom, 1972; MS099.011.002.026.00004 (Box 26)
    - Allston/Brighton neighborhood health clinic, 1978 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.026.00005 (Box 26)
    - Resources department, Miss Eva Gergora, 1971; MS099.011.002.026.00006 (Box 26)
    - Rehabilitation - speech and hearing, 1972; MS099.011.002.026.00007 (Box 26)
    - Speech and Hearing Center budget file, 1977; MS099.011.002.026.00008 (Box 26)
    - Pediatric office renovation center 4 A/S file, 1980; MS099.011.002.026.00009 (Box 26)
    - Pediatric waiting center 4 budget, 1977; MS099.011.002.026.00010 (Box 26)
    - Decoration and redecoration file A/S file, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.011.002.026.00011 (Box 26)
    - Personnel office - 37 Bennet Street, 1976; MS099.011.002.026.00012 (Box 26)
    - 37 Bennet Street 2 and 3 budget file, 1977; MS099.011.002.026.00013 (Box 26)
    - 37 Bennet Street 3rd floor conference room, 1982; MS099.011.002.026.00014 (Box 26)
    - 37 Bennet Street, 2nd floor ESD measurements, 1978; MS099.011.002.026.00015 (Box 26)
    - Medical Clinic Center 1, 1976; MS099.011.002.026.00016 (Box 26)
    - Cafeteria renvoations center basement, 1971; MS099.011.002.026.00017 (Box 26)
    - Speech and Hearing department Center 2nd, A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.026.00018 (Box 26)
    - Hemenway - 4th floor, 1980 -- 1981; MS099.011.002.026.00019 (Box 26)
    - 193-197 Harrison Avenue A/S file, 1977; MS099.011.002.026.00020 (Box 26)
    - Veterinary school, 203 Harrison Avenue 1st floor, 1980; MS099.011.002.026.00021 (Box 26)
    - Dr. Gellis office, 1980; MS099.011.002.026.00022 (Box 26)
    - Handicapped accessibility, general, 1981; MS099.011.002.026.00023 (Box 26)
    - Graphics account A/S file, 1979 -- 1981; MS099.011.002.026.00024 (Box 26)
    - Emergency room, 1974 -- 1979; MS099.011.002.026.00025 (Box 26)
    - Furniture, 1979; MS099.011.002.026.00026 (Box 26)
    - Emergency room suite, 1974 -- 1977; MS099.011.002.026.00027 (Box 26)
    - 8th floor dental tower clinic lab blood bank, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.011.002.026.00028 (Box 26)
    - Dental furniture, 1972; MS099.011.002.026.00029 (Box 26)
    - Directories A/S file, 1977 -- 1981; MS099.011.002.026.00030 (Box 26)
    - Hemenway House field measurements, 1971; MS099.011.002.026.00031 (Box 26)
    - Executive suite toilet Holmes 2 A/S file, 1978; MS099.011.002.026.00032 (Box 26)